[
  {
    "subject": "Matematika",
    "theme": "Tabulka úhlů"
  },
  {
    "question": "sin 0°",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "cos 0°",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "sin 30°",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "cos 30°",
    "answer": "√3/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "sin 45°",
    "answer": "√2/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "cos 45°",
    "answer": "√2/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "sin 60°",
    "answer": "√3/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "cos 60°",
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "question": "sin 90°",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "cos 90°",
    "answer": "0"
  }

]
